tutorabc.com 2009-03-27

# TutorABC - Your online language learning partner! Real people, real connection and real results!

---|---  

| 

| 

**Privacy**  
  
---  
|   
---  
  
  * **Your Personal Profile**  
When we ask information of you, our primary interest is to provide you with more personalized service. We do not sell, rent or trade your name or personal details to other organizations unless you give us your permission to do so. You can always opt out of these services by simply updating your personal profile. You have the ability to change or update your personal information at any time. You can do this by going to your personal profile. Just login and click "My Account".

  * **Security measures**  
We use a secure server to encrypt credit card information before it is sent to us over the Internet. We also insist on password verification at sign-in to protect against unauthorized access to your personal profile and course history. If you leave the computer unattended without logging out of the site, we log you out automatically after some time has passed.

  * **Registration for a subscription**  
TutorABC offers English courses online at competitive prices. To take one of these courses, you need to become a member of TutorABC. You also need to supply us with credit card information, so that you can pay for the services you request. This information is encrypted on a secure server. 

  * **Cookies**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that we store on your computer's browser or hard drive. We use cookies to customize the site for your country and language. Our cookies do not collect additional information from your computer's browser or hard drive. Most browsers allow you the option of preventing cookies from being stored on your computer, though doing so will cause you to lose many of the benefits of TutorABC.You may be served cookies from our advertisers on our co-branded sites. We do not control, nor do we have access to any of the information they may collect.

  * **IP addresses and browser type**  
Our website logs your computer's IP address and browser type, but we do not link this data to anything that can personally identify you. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user remains anonymous. We log this information so that we can monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage, which help us constantly improve the design and layout of TutorABC.

  * **Links to other websites**  
This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TutorABC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the TutorABC website.

  * **Refer a friend**  
If you decide to refer a friend to our site as part of TutorABC contests or other promotions, we ask you for the friend's email address and give you the option of sending them a personal message. TutorABC will then send a one-time, automatically generated email message inviting your friend to visit our site. TutorABC stores the email address in your personal file solely for the purpose of crediting you if your friend becomes a member.

  * **The TutorABC privacy policy is subject to change. If we decide to change the way we collect, use or share information, we will take commercially reasonable steps to notify members by way of an email that explains the changes and gives them the choice as to whether or not we may use their information in the new manner. If you have any questions about this policy statement, or about any of TutorABC's other policies and practices, please contact us. Contact us[ here](http://www.tutorabc.com/tw/asp/contact_us.asp).**

  * **All legal questions regarding TutorABC and MuchTalk, Ltd.**

|   
  
Copyright © TutorABC All Rights Reserved.
